<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patterns on Infusion</title>
    <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patterns on Infusion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/installation/</guid>
      <description>Infusion is built using the static site engine, Hugo, and NPM. The codebase is available to download on Github. Let&amp;rsquo;s get everything installed step-by-step.
Install Hugo First you need to install Hugo globally.
OSX users If you are a Mac user and have Homebrew on your system, installing Hugo is simple:
brew install hugo Alternatively, you can manually install Hugo from a package. You can verify the installation was successful by typing:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/setup/</guid>
      <description>By now, you should have followed the  Installation instructions. You should have Hugo and Node installed, and a local copy of a forked version of Infusion. You should also have run npm install in the root of that codebase.
&amp;ldquo;Cleaning&amp;rdquo; the content folder Before you can start writing documentation, there are a few things still to do in order to get set up. At the moment, your version of Infusion is a facsimile of the original, containing all the content you&amp;rsquo;re reading right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/serving/</guid>
      <description>Serving locally While you&amp;rsquo;re creating content for your project, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably want to see what the finished product looks like. Fortunately, Infusion is easy to serve locally using the serve command:
npm run serve This will serve your working project from localhost:1313. Whenever you make changes to your files, the site will automatically rebuild. No need to refresh the web page!
Publishing on Github Pages Infusion creates a /docs folder containing the latest version of your site whenever you do an npm run build or a git commit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printing</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/printing/</guid>
      <description>Infusion&amp;rsquo;s output site includes a one-page  Print version of the generated library, available at /print-version. So, if your library base URL is https://yourName.github.io/your-library, you can print the whole library — to PDF if wanted — from the following address:
https://yourName.github.io/your-library/print-version     Print styles are also provided for individual pattern pages so, if you wanted to print off a single pattern document, you can!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating Infusion</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/updating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/updating/</guid>
      <description>The core of Infusion&amp;rsquo;s functionality is in its Hugo theme, also called Infusion. This is found in the theme folder.
 content docs lib snippets static themes  infusion    Do not &amp;ldquo;hack the core&amp;rdquo;. If you have any issues with Infusion, please report them to the Infusion Github repository and they will be dealt with ASAP.
Infusion is undergoing constant development, so keep an eye out for new releases.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>