<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patterns on Infusion</title>
    <link>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patterns on Infusion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/installation/</guid>
      <description>Infusion is built using the static site engine, Hugo, and NPM. The codebase is available to download on Github. Let&amp;rsquo;s get set up step-by-step.
1. Install Hugo First we need to install Hugo globally.
OSX users If you are a Mac user and have Homebrew on your system, installing Hugo is simple:
brew install hugo Alternatively, you can manually install Hugo from a package. You can verify the installation was successful by typing:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Library setup</title>
      <link>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/library-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/library-setup/</guid>
      <description>By now, you should have followed the Installation instructions. You should have Hugo and Node installed, and a local copy of a forked version of Infusion. You should also have run npm install in the root of that codebase.
&amp;ldquo;Cleaning&amp;rdquo; the content folder Before you can start documenting patterns, there are a few things still to do in order to get set up. At the moment, your version of Infusion is a facsimile of the original, containing all this documentation content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving</title>
      <link>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heydon.github.io/infusion/patterns/serving/</guid>
      <description>Serving locally While you&amp;rsquo;re creating content for your library, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably want to see what the finished product looks like. Fortunately, Infusion is easy to serve locally using the serve command:
npm run serve This will serve your working library from localhost:1313 (the exact URL will be determined by what&amp;rsquo;s in your baseURL and will be revealed to you by your terminal). Whenever you make changes to your library&amp;rsquo;s files, the site will automatically rebuild.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>